

OVERVIEW

Hi im Daniel, a graphic and web designer. My career choices was made the day I picked up a camera to film me and my friends on a skateboard, and create silly videos and edits of our past times. We were young and had fun. I fell in love with digital arts and digital media and knew this would be my future.

As a creative and artist I found that no task is impossible if you do your research, get creative and keep it simple.

My passion and job interests lie in the digital design, web programming and design, and 3D modeling.

I have been working as a web designer and developer for four years, and I've completed mutliple website builds and publishments for companies and clients including; Enterprise Outsourcuing, Secured Enterprise, HR Artis, Financeapps Astralfoods, Sabvest capital and more.

HOBBIES

Photoshop manipulations
Drawing and doodling
3D Modeling
Outdoor Activities
Video and photography
Web design research and trends
Learning new skills

DANIEL VAN DEN BERG GRAPHIC AND WEB DESIGNER

EXPERIENCE

LOR Technologies WordPress and Front-End Developer

June 2023 - Present Johannesburg Area, South Africa

Front-end Development and WordPress Developer for clients base. Notable clients include C2Group, Crystalfusion, UASA, Tribeca Coffee Company, Pro-Gressio life coaching, Class Signs Signage. Wordpress websites varied from basic brochures to custom e-commerce solutions

MDH Digital

WordPress and Front-End Developer/Technical Assistant

December 2022 - June 2023

Johannesburg Area, South Africa

Front-end Development and WordPress Developer for clients base. Notable clients included UASA, Bikewise, Graffiti. Other responsibilities included assiting and managing other front-end developers and general IT support around the office.

Hyperbolic WordPress and Front-End Developer

June 2022 - November 2022 Fully Remote

Front-end Development and WordPress Developer for clients base. Notable clients included Cairnmead and USN - eCommerce website. Other skills i've gained during this time include working with Bubble and NocoDB.

eNew Media Graphic and Web Designer

February 2018 - May 2022 (4 and 4 months) Johannesburg Area, South Africa

Building and maintaining company web pages and outsourcing clients' webpage creation and maintenance.

Website creation includes, strategy and planning, wireframe construction, designing and building according to design in web languages including HTML, CSS, and JS, PHP and website builders such as Wordpress, templates, etc.

Ad creation for marketing purposes on company social media pages and company news reports and articles on websites.

Graphic designs including brochures, logos, packaging, creation for companies Cl's, website designs, social media ads and design principles throughout.

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop	7 yrs
Adobe Illustrator	7 yrs
Adobe Indesign	4 yrs
Adobe Animate	2 yrs
Adobe Dreamweaver	6 yrs
Adobe Premiere Pro	4 yrs
Adobe After Effects	4 yrs
Adobe Media Encoder	4 yrs
Adobe XD/Figma	4 yrs
Blender	2 yrs

Web Languages

HTML	7 yrs
JavaScript	4 yrs
CSS	7 yrs
PHP	3 yrs
Wordpress	5 yrs
Bootstrap	5 yrs
Responsive Designs	7 yrs
Domain SEO and	5 yrs
optimizations	
Actively learning React,	Redux,
Node and more.	

PERSONAL INFO

Mobile Number 067 847 5162

Email Address danievdb101danny@gmail.com

Citizen Status SA Citizen

ID Number 9701125127088

Ethnicity White

Languages Afrikaans English

LocationJohannesburg Area

SOCIAL INFO













Matrix wharehouse IT Technical Support

December 2017 - January 2018 (2 months) Pretoria, Monument park

Lamda Printing Junior Graphic Designer

June 2016 - September 2016 (4 months) August 2017 - October 2017 (3 months Polokwane

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts - BA - Graphic Design CTU Training Solutions Polokwane 2016-2018

Matric 2015 Komatipoort Akademie 2004-2015



CERTIFICATIONS

Adobe Certified, Web Authoring Using Adobe Dreamweaver
Adobe Certified, Visual Communication Using Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Certified, Rich Animated Media using Adobe Animate
Adobe Certified, Graphic Design & Illustration in Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Certified in Digital Video Using Adobe Premiere Pro
Google Skillshop Web Creative Certification
Google Skillshop Analytics Individual Qualification
Google Skillshop Ads Display Certification
Google Skillshop Mobile Experience Certification Exam
Google Skillshop Google My Business
FreeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design Certification
+ More to come



REFERENCES

C2 Group
Dave Madden - Sales
+27 71 686 2180

CTU Training Solutions Lucienne Malete - Facilitator 067 932 9216

Komatipoort Akademie Highschool 013 793 7304